module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Call center for GM where I had to tell a pregnant woman that she wasn\'t entitled to any financial assistance for a GM repair shop ruining their engine', 
    a: 'JLowe',
    b: 'JoshP',
    c: 'Adam',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Dog Kennel Cleaner', 
    a: 'Tyler N',
    b: 'BDF',
    c: 'Billy',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Janitor for a themepark', 
    a: 'RA',
    b: 'Joe',
    c: 'Dante',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Fabric Cutter at Joannâ€™s. You don\'t understand how much lint gets on you.', 
    a: 'Marion',
    b: 'Darice',
    c: 'Shannon',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Ballroom Dancing Assistant Instructor', 
    a: 'Mark',
    b: 'Devon',
    c: 'Jessica',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Apple Call Center', 
    a: 'Tyler N',
    b: 'Glynn',
    c: 'Sean',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Xbox Live Retention Specialist', 
    a: 'Brady',
    b: 'Kell',
    c: 'Jalaliani',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Cashier at Family Christian Bookstores', 
    a: 'Brandon',
    b: 'James',
    c: 'Jessica',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Working at a bagel shop, making sandwiches and always having to clean cream cheese off surfaces', 
    a: 'West',
    b: 'Tomi',
    c: 'Jessica',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Roofing in West Texas Summer', 
    a: 'Joe',
    b: 'Troy',
    c: 'Mark',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'a'
  },
];
